<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<nailbar>
  <services name="Manicure">
    <entree>
      <item>Regular Polish</item>
      <description>Polish: Our experienced nail technicians will expertly paiting your nails
                with a polish of your choice. </description>
      <price>5.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Shellac Nails Polish</item>
      <description>Treat your nails to this unique hybridized nail polish for a flawless finish.
                Shellac nails offers a gentle gel alternative, without sacrificing the long-lasting benefits.
                As thin as polish, shellac is UV cured for resilient and enviable shine. </description>
      <price>25.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Shellac Nails French Polish</item>
      <description>The Manicure French Finish treatment. Adorning your nails with the classic french tip finish,
                for an elegant finish that lasts no matter your schedule.</description>
      <price>30.00</price>
    </entree>
  </services>
  <services name="Pedicure">
    <entree>
      <item>Mini-Pedicure</item>
      <description>A quick fix for those on the go our Mini-Manicure restores nails in no time, without compromising on perfection.
                Enjoy a shape and buff, as well as essential cuticle work before finishing with regular polish.</description>
      <price>35.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Shellac Toes Polish</item>
      <description>Get sandal ready with our Shellac Toenails treatment. Add a touch of glamour with long-lasting results suitable for the promenade or the dinner party.
                Pair with one of our indulgent pedicure experiences for total foot renewal.</description>
      <price>30.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Shellac Toes French Polish</item>
      <description>The Pedicure French Finish treatment. Adorning your nails with the classic french tip finish,
                for an elegant finish that lasts no matter your schedule.</description>
      <price>35.00</price>
    </entree>
  </services>
  <services name="Extras">
    <entree>
      <item>Refill</item>
      <description>Refills your gel nails</description>
      <price>25.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Removel Gel Nails</item>
      <description>Remove gel nails polish.</description>
      <price>15.00</price>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <item>Removel Shellac</item>
      <description>Remove Shellac polish using special non-toxic products</description>
      <price>8.00</price>
    </entree>
  </services>
  <therapists name="Therapist">
    <entree>
      <name>Juliana</name>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <name>Claire</name>
    </entree>
    <entree>
      <name>Rachel</name>
    </entree>
  </therapists>
</nailbar>