<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="NailBar.xsl"?>
<catalog>
  <menu item="1">
    <service_type>File and Polish</service_type>
   <description>File and Polish: Our experienced nail technicians will expertly cut and shape your nails,
    finishing with a polish of your choice. </description>
       <price>15.00</price>    
  </menu>
   <menu item="2">
    <service_type>Regular Polish</service_type>
    <description>Polish: Our experienced nail technicians will expertly paiting your nails 
    with a polish of your choice. </description>
       <price>5.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="3">
    <service_type>Shellac Nails Polish</service_type>
    <description>Treat your nails to this unique hybridized nail polish for a flawless finish. 
    Shellac nails offers a gentle gel alternative, without sacrificing the long-lasting benefits. 
    As thin as polish, shellac is UV cured for resilient and enviable shine. </description>
    <price>25.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="4">
    <service_type>Shellac Nails French Polish</service_type>
    <description>The Manicure French Finish treatment. Adorning your nails with the classic french tip finish, 
    for an elegant finish that lasts no matter your schedule.</description>
       <price>30.00</price>    
  </menu>
 <menu item="5">
    <service_type>Shellac Toes French Polish</service_type>
    <description>The Pedicure French Finish treatment. Adorning your nails with the classic french tip finish, 
    for an elegant finish that lasts no matter your schedule. </description>
       <price>35.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="6">
    <service_type>Shellac Toes Polish</service_type>
    <description>Get sandal ready with our Shellac Toenails treatment. Add a touch of glamour with long-lasting results suitable for the promenade or the dinner party. 
    Pair with one of our indulgent pedicure experiences for total foot renewal.</description>
       <price>30.00</price>
   <menu item="7">
    <service_type>Full Manicure</service_type>
    <description>Indulge with our signature manicure at Nail Bar. This popular treatment involves nail shape work, a nail strengthening bath and cuticle detail. Hands are lightly exfoliated with our scrub, full of natural protein peelings, working to restore the protective skin layer. 
    Finish with an enriching massage with a moisturizer and polish of your choice. </description>
       <price>30.00</price>
    
  </menu>
 <menu item="8">
    <service_type>Full Pedicure</service_type>
    <description>Rest and recuperate whilst we breathe life back into your tired feet. A relaxing Jacuzzi bath, with a unique blend of herbs and essential oils, allows you to unwind, followed by callus work, nail clipping, filling and cuticle work for healthy looking toes. 
    Pedi exfoliating foot scrub removes dry and flaking skin, revealing soft and smooth soles. 
    Pedi Skin protectant lotion is massaged into your feet to repair and enrich with essential moisture, 
    finishing off with a paint of polish. </description>
       <price>50.00</price>    
  </menu>
   <menu item="9">
    <service_type>Gel Nails</service_type>
    <description>Explore new lengths with our selection of gel nail extensions. 
    Choose innovative gel/acrylic hybrid PolyGel and let our technicians mould the nails of your desires with a 
    lightweight finish, or go back to classics with our standard UV-cured gel extensions. </description>
       <price>50.00</price>    
  </menu>
   <menu item="10">
    <service_type>Refill</service_type>
    <description>Refills your gel nails </description>
       <price>25.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="11">
    <service_type>Removel Gel Nails</service_type>
    <description>Remove gel nails polish. </description>
       <price>15.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="12">
    <service_type>Removel Shellac</service_type>
    <description>Remove Shellac polish </description>
       <price>8.00</price>    
  </menu>
  <menu item="13">
    <service_type>Art Design</service_type>
    <description>Create art of the nails/toes </description>
       <price>5.00</price>    
  </menu>
 <menu item="14">
    <service_type>Mini-Manicure</service_type>
    <description>A quick fix for those on the go our Mini-Manicure restores nails in no time, without compromising on perfection. 
    Enjoy a shape and buff, as well as essential cuticle work before finishing with regular polish.</description>
       <price>25.00</price>    
  </menu>
 <menu item="15">
    <service_type>Mini-Pedicure</service_type>
    <description>A quick fix for those on the go our Mini-Manicure restores nails in no time, without compromising on perfection. 
    Enjoy a shape and buff, as well as essential cuticle work before finishing with regular polish. </description>
       <price>35.00</price>    
  </menu>  
  </catalog>